(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(ELECTRONIC SURGE THUMPS)
(STEADY BEEPING)
(CLANK)
(RUMBLING)
(WHOOSHING)
(CLANK)
(ELECTRONIC BEEPING)
(CROWD MURMURING)
(ELECTRIC SURGE THUMPS)
(FOOTSTEPS THUDDING)
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(FEMALE VOICE) Read the charges.
Dr. Jumba Jookiba,
lead scientist of
Galaxy Defense Industries,
you stand before this council
accused of illegal
genetic experimentation.
(ELECTRONIC WHIRRING)
(THUD)
GRAND COUNCILWOMAN:
How do you plead?
Not guilty!
My experiments are only theoretical,
completely within legal boundaries.
We believe you actually created something.
Created something? Ha!
But that would be
irresponsible and unethical.
I would never, ever...
(WHOOSHES SOFTLY)
...make more than one.
(GROWLING AND SNARLING)
(CLANKS)
(ALL GASPING)
What is that monstrosity?
Monstrosity?
What you see before you is
the first of a new species.
I call it experiment 6-2-6.
(SNARLING)
JUMBA: He is bulletproof, fireproof
and can think faster than supercomputer.
He can see in the dark
and move objects 3,000 times his size.
His only instinct,
to destroy everything he touches!
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
So, it is a monster.
Hey, just a little one.
It is an affront to nature.
It must be destroyed!
Calm yourself, Captain Gantu.
Perhaps it can be reasoned with.
Experiment 6-2-6,
give us some sign
you understand any of this.
Show us that there is something
inside you that is good.
(CLEARING THROAT)
ALL: Hmm?
Meega, nala kweesta!
(HORRIFIED GASPS)
(RETCHING)
So naughty!
(CACKLING SINISTERLY)
I didn't teach it that.
Place that idiot scientist under arrest!
I prefer to be called "evil genius"!
And as for that abomination...
(SLURPING)
...it is the flawed product
of a deranged mind.
- (GLASS SQUEAKING)
- It has no place among us.
Captain Gantu, take him away.
With pleasure.
(KNUCKLES CRACKING)
(MUTTERING)
(CLANKING)
(SNARLING)
(SQUEAKS)
(JABBERING)
(YELPS)
Hmm.
(GURGLING)
(CLANKING AND WHIRRING)
(SNORTING)
Uncomfortable?
Oh... Good!
The council has banished you
to exile on a desert asteroid.
So, relax... Enjoy the trip
and don't get any ideas.
These guns are locked
onto your genetic signature.
They won't shoot anyone but you.
(FEROCIOUS SNARL)
- Ow! Why, you...
- (CLEARING THROAT)
May I remind the Captain
that he is on duty.
(PISTOL SQUEAKS AND POPS)
Secure the cell!
Aye, captain.
(WHIRS AND THUDS)
(HATCH WHIRS SHUT)
FEMALE OFFICER: Captain on deck.
All ahead full.
(SEAT CUSHION HISSES)
(CONTROLS BEEPING)
Do... Does this, uh, look infected to you?
(ENGINE WHOOSHING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS)
(GUNS WHIRRING)
(CLICKING AND WHIRRING)
Oh!
(THROATY GURGLING)
(HIGH-PITCHED SQUEAL)
(GURGLING AND WHIRRING CONTINUE)
Quiet, you.
(GROWLING AND SNORTING)
- Gunfire in the cell bay!
- Open a channel.
(TEETH CHATTERING)
(CHUCKLING)
(WHIMPERING)
(GUNS ZAPPING)
- (ALARM BUZZING)
- He's loose on Deck C!
Red alert. Seal off the deck!
(YELPS, GRUNTS)
(WHIMPERING)
(GRUNTING)
Security, converge on Door 7!
GANTU OVER INTERCOM:
Deadly force authorized. Fire on sight!
There he is!
(SQUEALING)
Security to bridge.
It's in the ventilation system.
(FOOTSTEPS CLICKING)
- He's headed for the power...
- (ENGINES WHINING)
...grid.
(LOUD THUD, WHOOSHING)
What was that?
I don't think he's on the ship anymore.
Confirmed. He's taken a police cruiser.
(ALARM BEEPING)
Yeah... He took the red one.
(HORN HONKING)
Yee-haw!
(WEAPON FIRE CRACKLING)
(YELLING)
(WEAPONS ZAPPING)
(WHOOSHING)
(GRUNTS)
(ENGINES WHINING)
Hmm?
PILOT: That's it! We got it. We got it!
(SHOUTING AND LAUGHING)
COMPUTER VOICE:
Hyperdrive activated. System charging.
He's engaged his H-drive!
COMPUTER: Warning,
guidance is not functional.
Pursuit Commander, that crazy trog
is about to make a jump!
COMMANDER: Break formation!
Get clear of that ship!
Navigation failure. Do not engage hyper...
(THUNDEROUS EXPLOSION)
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
(POUNDS CHAIR)
(FRUSTRATED SIGH)
Get me Galactic Control.
(DOOR WHOOSHES)
Where is he?
He's still in hyperspace.
Where will he exit?
Calculating now.
Quadrant 17, section 0-0-5, area 51.
A planet called... Ee-arth.
I want an expert on this planet
in here now!
(MONITOR BEEPING)
What is that?
Water. Most of the planet
is covered in it.
He won't survive in water.
His molecular density is too great.
(RELIEVED SIGHS)
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
No...
(BELL DINGING)
(CLAMORING)
Of course.
How much time do we have?
We have projected his landing
at three hours, 42 minutes.
Oh, we have to gas the planet.
Hold it! Hold everything!
Earth is a protected wildlife preserve.
Yeah. We've been using it
to rebuild the mosquito population
which, need I remind you,
is an endangered species!
Am I to assume you are the expert?
(LAUGHING MODESTLY)
Oh, I don't know about "expert."
(CLEARS THROAT)
Agent Pleakley at your service.
Can we not simply destroy the island?
No! Crazyhead!
The mosquito's food of choice,
primitive humanoid life forms,
have colonies all over that planet.
Are they intelligent?
No, but they're very delicate.
In fact, every time an asteroid strikes
their planet,
they have to begin life all over.
(SIGHS)
It's fascinating, isn't it?
With this, I've been able to study...
What if our military forces
just landed there?
Well, that'd be a bad idea!
These are extremely
simple creatures, miss.
Landing there would create
mass mayhem and planet-wide panic!
A quiet capture would require
an understanding of 6-2-6
that we do not possess!
Who, then, Mr. Pleakley,
would you send for his extraction?
Does he have a brother?
Close grandmother, perhaps?
(ANGRY SHOUTING)
(INSANE JABBERING)
Friendly cousin?
Neighbor with a beard?
(INMATES CHANTING FURIOUSLY)
(WHIRRING)
(ELECTRICAL HUMMING)
(ENRAGED ROARING)
- (GOBBLING)
- (SNIFFLES)
(JUMBA MURMURING)
(LAUGHING SINISTERLY)
He got away?
I'm sure this comes as no surprise to you.
I designed this creature
for to be unstoppable.
Which is precisely why
you must now bring him back.
What? Me?
And to reward you,
we are willing to trade
your freedom for his capture.
(SIGHS)
6-2-6 will not come easily.
Maybe direct hit from plasma cannon
might stun him long enough to...
Plasma cannon granted.
Do we have a bargain, Dr. Jumba?
(GRUNTS)
B- b-but it's a delicate planet!
(SINGSONG) Who's going to control him?
You will.
Very good, your highness.
- I... I didn't quite...
- (DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
Uh, you're not joking!
So, tell me, my little one-eyed one,
on what poor, pitiful, defenseless planet
has my monstrosity been unleashed?
MAN WITH CHORUS: Mahalo Nui la
Ke Ali Iwahine
O Lili Ulani
O Ka Wohi Ku
Ka Pipio Mai O Ke Anuenue
Na Waihooluu A Halikeole
E Nana Na Maka I Ke Ao Malama
Mai Hawall Akea I Kauai...
(HULA DRUMS BEATING
MIDTEMPO RHYTHM)
(MAN SHOUTS JOYOUSLY
IN HAWAllAN)
MAN: O Kal'kaua He Inoa
O Ka Pua Mae Ole I Ka I'
Ka Pua Maila I Ka Mauna
I Ke Kuahiwi O Mauna Kea
Ke 'Maila I K'lauea
M'lamalama I Wahinekapu
A Ka Luna O Uw'kahuna
I Ka Pali Kapu O Ka Auea
MAN AND CHORUS:
Ea Mai Ke Ali I Kia Manu
Ua Wehi I Ka Hulu O Ka Mamo
Ka Pua Nani A O Hawai I
O Kal'kaua He Inoa
CHORUS: O Kal'kaua He Inoa
Ka Pua Mae Ole I Ka I'
Ka Pua Maila I Ka Mauna
I Ke Kuahiwi O Mauna Kea
(SPEAKING HAWAllAN)
Ke 'Maila I K'lauea...
One, two, three, four...
...M'lamalama I Wahinekapu...
Ay-yi-yi.
...A Ka Luna O Uw'kahuna
I Ka Pali Kapu O Ka Auea
MAN AND CHORUS: Mahalo Nui la
Ke Ali Iwahine
O Lili Ulani
O Ka Wohi Ku...
Ea Mai Ke Ali I Kia Manu
Ua Wehi I Ka Hulu O Ka Mamo
Ka Pua Nani A O Hawai I
O Kal'kaua He Inoa...
ALL: He inoa no kalani
Kalakaua kulele.
- Whoa!
(WOMEN GASP)
INSTRUCTOR: Stop. Stop.
Lilo, why are you all wet?
It's sandwich day.
(SIGHING)
Every Thursday, I take Pudge the fish
a peanut butter sandwich.
Pudge is a fish?
And today we were out of peanut butter!
So I asked my sister what to give him
and she said a tuna sandwich.
I can't give Pudge tuna!
(WHISPERING) Do you know what tuna is?
- Fish?
- It's fish!
If I gave Pudge tuna,
I'd be an abomination!
I'm late because I had to go to the store
and get peanut butter
'cause all we have is stinkin' tuna!
Lilo, Lilo, why is this so important?
Pudge controls the weather.
- You're crazy.
- (LILO SHRIEKING)
- (ALL SCREAMING)
- Please! Please!
Everybody calm down!
- (CRYING)
- Girls...
(SPEAKING HAWAllAN)
Shh.
- Lilo...
- I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I won't do it again!
Maybe we should call your sister.
No! I'll be good! I want to dance.
I practiced.
I just want to dance.
Ooh, she bit me.
GIRLS: Eww!
(ALL CHEERING)
(GIRLS LAUGHING AND SHOUTING)
I called your sister.
She said to wait for her
here on the porch.
We'll try again on Sunday.
(CHILDREN SHOUTING PLAYFULLY
IN DISTANCE)
Does this look infected to you?
Yeah.
(GIRLS GASPING)
You better not have rabies.
If you have rabies,
the dogcatcher is going to have to cut...
Are you going to play dolls?
You don't have a doll.
This is Scrump.
(ALL GASPING)
I made her, but her head is too big.
So I pretend a bug laid eggs
in her ears, and she's upset
because she only has a few more days to...
(SOFT, SAD MUSIC PLAYING)
Lilo!
Lilo?
Oh, no.
(GRUNTS)
You better be home.
(DOG BARKING)
(ENGINE PURRING)
- (BRAKES SCREECH)
- Hey! Watch where you're going!
Stupidhead!
(PANTING)
(ELVIS PRESLEY'S
"HEARTBREAK HOTEL" PLAYING)
I Found A New Place To Dwell...
Oh, Lilo!
Lilo! Open the door, Lilo!
LILO: Go away.
...You Make Me So Lonely, Baby... ♪
Lilo? We don't have time for this.
...I Get So Lonely...
Leave me alone to die.
Come on, Lilo that social worker's
going to be here any minute!
...You Still Can Find...
(VOLUME INCREASES)
...Some Room...
(GROWLING)
For Brokenhearted Lovers
To Cry Away Their Gloom
(FRUSTRATED GROAN)
Don't Make Me So Lonely
I Get So Lonely I Could Die...
(ENGINE TURNS OFF)
(WOOD CREAKING)
- (GRUNTS)
- The Bellhop's Tears Keep Flowin'...
You are so finished when I get in there!
(MOUTHING SONG)
Well, They Been So Long
On Lonely Street
They Ain't Ever Gonna Look Back...
Oh, I'm going to stuff you in the blender,
push "puree,"
then bake you into a pie
and feed it to the social worker!
And when he says, "Mmm, this is great.
What's your secret?" I'm going to say...
(GASPS)
"Love... And nurturing."
Hi. Uh...
(HAMMER CLUNKS)
You must be the, uh...
The stupidhead.
Oh! Oh...
Oh, you know, I'm really sorry about that
and if I'd known who you were,
of course I never would've...
Uh... I can pay for that.
It's a rental.
Are you the guardian in question?
Yes. I'm Nani.
Nice to meet you, Mister...
Bubbles.
Mr. Bubbles. That's a strange...
Yes, I know.
Are you going to invite me in, Nani?
Uh... I thought we could
sit out here and talk.
I don't think so.
(QUIETLY) Right. Uh...
(FROM INSIDE)
...It's Always Crowded...
This way.
...You Still Can Find Some Room
For Brokenhearted Lovers
To Cry Away Their Gloom
You Make Me So Lonely, Baby...
Uh... Wait here.
(CLATTERING)
(GLASS BREAKING, CRASHING)
- (RECORD SCRATCHES, MUSIC STOPS)
- LILO: Hey!
(CLUNKING)
(PANTING) So... Lemonade?
Do you often leave your sister home alone?
No. Never.
(NANI SHRIEKS)
Well, except for just now.
Uh, I had to run to the store
to get some...
- (STEAM WHISTLING)
- Oh!
You left the stove on while you were out?
Low heat! Just a simmer.
Mmm! It's coming along great.
- (LOUD WHOOSH, YELLS)
- I found that this morning.
Lilo! There you are.
Honeyface... This is Mr. Bubbles.
Nice to meet you.
Your knuckles say "Cobra."
(CRACKING)
Cobra Bubbles.
You don't look like a social worker.
I'm a special classification.
Did you ever kill anyone?
We're getting off the subject.
Let's talk about you. Are you happy?
(NO AUDIO)
I'm adjusted. I eat four food groups
and look both ways
before crossing the street
and take long naps and get disciplined.
- (MUFFLED GASP)
- Disciplined?
Yeah. She disciplines me real good.
Sometimes five times a day.
- With bricks.
- No...
Bricks?
Uh-huh, in a pillowcase.
Okay! That's enough sugar for you.
Why don't you run along, you little cutie.
(NERVOUS GIGGLE)
The other social workers
just thought she was a scream.
Thirsty?
Let me illuminate to you
the precarious situation
in which you have found yourself.
I am the one they call
when things go wrong,
and things have indeed gone wrong.
(SPOONS CLINKING)
(RATTLING)
My friends need to be punished.
(GROANS)
Call me next time you're left here alone.
Yep.
In case you're wondering,
this did not go well.
(NAILS CLATTERING)
You have three days to change my mind.
(SHRIEKING)
(SHRIEKING CONTINUES)
- Blah.
- Eww!
Lilo!
(BOOTS SCREECH)
(HINGES CREAK/DOOR SHUTS)
(SLAMS)
(HINGES CREAKS)
(LILO GROWLS)
(SNARLING AND GROWLING)
(HISSES)
Why didn't you wait at the school?
You were supposed to wait there!
- Lilo!
- (GRUNTING)
Do you not understand?
Do you want to be taken away?
Answer me!
- No!
- No, you don't understand?
- No, what?
No!
(GRUNTS)
(MUFFLED WHINING)
(FRUSTRATED GRUNT)
You're such a pain!
So why don't you sell me
and buy a rabbit instead?
At least a rabbit would behave
better than you!
Go ahead! Then you'll be happy
because it'll be smarter than me, too!
And quieter!
You'll like it,
'cause it's stinky, like you!
(SLAMS)
Go to your room!
I'm already in my room!
(SLAMS)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(SOFTLY) Hey.
I brought you some pizza,
in case you were hungry.
We're a broken family, aren't we?
No.
Maybe, a little.
Maybe a lot.
I shouldn't have yelled at you.
We're sisters. It's our job.
Yeah, well, from now on...
I like you better as a sister than a mom.
Yeah?
And you like me better as a sister
than a rabbit, right?
(SNIFFLING)
(GENTLY) Oh...
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Yes.
Yes, I do.
(SNIFFLES)
I hit Mertle Edmonds today.
You hit her?
Before I bit her.
You bit her. Lilo, you shouldn't...
People treat me different.
They just don't know what to say.
I'll tell you what.
If you promise not to fight anymore
I promise not to yell at you,
except on special occasions.
Tuesdays and bank holidays would be good.
Yeah? Would that be good?
(BOTH GIGGLING)
Oh! My camera's full again.
(WHISPERING) Aren't they beautiful?
(LOW RUMBLING)
(ELECTRICAL CRACKLING)
(RUMBLING CONTINUING)
(THUNDERING WHOOSH)
A falling star!
(CAR ALARMS BLARING IN DISTANCE)
(WHOOSHING)
(EXPLOSIVE THUD)
I call it! Get out! Get out!
I have to make a wish!
Can't you go any faster?
Oh, no! Gravity is increasing on me.
No, it's not!
It is, too, Lilo.
The same thing happened yesterday.
You rotten sister!
Your butt is crushing me!
Why do you act so weird?
(SLAMS)
(QUIETLY) It's me again.
I need someone to be my friend...
Someone who won't run away.
Maybe send me an angel...
The nicest angel you have.
(FLAMES ROARING)
(SHOUTING IN ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
(SNIFFING)
(FEET PATTERING)
- (PLOPPING)
- (PISTOL ZINGS)
(PLOPPING)
(PISTOL ZINGS)
(GROWLS)
- (FROG CROAKING)
- (WEAPONS COCK)
(SHOUTING IN ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(LOUD RUMBLING)
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING AND GROANING)
What we when hit?
There it is.
It stay jammed under the fender.
(ALIEN GROANS, DRIVERS GASP)
We better call somebody.
(GROANS)
(GROANING)
- (WHIMPERING)
- (GASPS)
(ALL WHIMPERING)
(GROWLS)
(GASPS)
(SHOUTING IN ALIEN LANGUAGE)
- (SHOUTING)
- (WHIMPERING)
NANl: We're looking for something
that can defend itself...
Something that won't die...
Something sturdy, you know?
Like a lobster.
Lilo, you lolo. Do we have a lobster door?
No. We have a dog door.
We are getting a dog.
(FRANTIC GRUNTING)
(JUMBA LAUGHS IN DISTANCE)
JUMBA: So nice to see
your pretty face again!
Jumba?
We need your name and address
at the bottom of the form...
The kennel's back this way.
Go. Pick someone out.
(ECHOING) Hello?
(THUMPING)
Are there any "aminals" in here?
(PANTING AND WHINING)
(SNIFFING)
LILO: Hello!
Hi.
Hoh... Ha...
Hi...
Wow!
Oh, yes. Mm-hmm.
All of our dogs are adoptable.
Except that one!
What is that thing?
A dog, I think.
But it was dead this morning.
It was dead this morning?
Well, we thought it was dead.
It was hit by a truck.
I like him! Come here, boy.
(STRAINING GROWL)
Oh! Aah!
(GRUNTS)
Wouldn't you like a different dog?
We have better dogs, dear.
Not better than him.
He can talk! Say hello.
He... Hel...
Dogs can't talk, dear.
LILO: He did.
Does it have to be this dog?
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
(SMACKING)
Yes, he's good. I can tell.
WOMAN: You'll have to think
of a name for him.
His name is... Stitch.
- Now, that's not a real name...
- Hmm. Uh-uh, uh-uh-uh.
...In Iceland...
But here, it's a good name.
Stitch it is.
And there's a two dollar license fee.
I want to buy him!
(WHISPERING) Can I borrow two dollars?
He's all yours.
JUMBA: You're all mine.
PLEAKLEY: Well, what's he doing?
Shh! Keep quiet. He's listening for us.
(WHISPERING) How good
is his hearing? I mean, can he...
(GRUNTS)
(CHOKING)
(LASER HUMS)
Why don't you run?
(BARKING)
Coming! I'm coming!
Stop!
I have just determined this situation
to be far too hazardous!
Don't worry, I won't hit her.
No! That girl is a part
of the mosquito food chain.
Here! Educate yourself.
Using a little girl for a shield.
This is low, even for you!
- (TAUNTINGLY) Whoo-hoo!
- Bah!
(YELLS)
Tear him apart
with all both my bare hands!
- Have you lost your mind?
- (BARKING)
What is it, Stitch?
We cannot be seen!
(BARKING)
- Bad dog, barking at nothing!
- (MUTTERING)
You can't shoot, and you can't be seen.
Look at you!
(WHISPERING) You look like a monster.
We have to blend in.
NANl: Okay, I got to get to work.
Stick around town
and stay out of the roads, okay?
- I'll meet you at 1:00.
- Hmm?
Oh! Ah!
(CHUCKLING)
(GROWLING AND SNARLING)
NANI: Okay, I guess we should be going.
(RASPBERRY KISS)
(GIGGLES) What about stitch?
(DISGUSTED GRUNT)
(BICYCLE BELL CHIMES)
(GROWLS)
(GASPS)
My friends!
(GASPING AND SHRIEKING)
(ALL PANTING)
What do you want?
I'm sorry I bit you and pulled your hair
and punched you in the face.
Apology not accepted.
Now get out of my way
before I run you over.
(SHRIEKS)
I got a new dog. His name is Stitch.
That is the ugliest thing I have ever saw.
- Yeah.
Eww! Get it away from me!
I'm gonna get a disease!
(STITCH GASPS)
(SHRIEKS)
(CRYING)
Somebody do something!
Oh, great! He's loose.
His destructive programming
is taking effect.
He will be irresistibly drawn
to large cities
where he will back up sewers,
reverse street signs
and steal everyone's left shoe.
(SNARLING)
(FRUSTRATED GRUNTING)
It's nice to live on an island
with no large cities.
(GASPS)
(BABBLING)
Are you okay?
(ROCK INTRO TO ELVIS PRESLEY
SINGING "STUCK ON YOU")
Doo-doo
You Can Shake An Apple
Off An Apple Tree
Shake-a, Shake-a, Sugar,
But You'll Never Shake Me
Uh-uh-uh
Doo-doo-doo
No, Siree, Uh-uh...
- Uh-uh.
- ...Doo-doo-doo
Doo-doo-doo
I'm Gonna Stick Like Glue
Stick Because I'm...
Stuck On You
I'm Gonna Run My Fingers
Through Your Long, Black hair...
Hey, over here, little buddy.
...Squeeze You Tighter
Than A Grizzly Bear
- Uh-uh-uh
- Doo-doo-doo
Yes, Siree, Uh-huh
Doo-doo-doo, Doo-doo-doo
I'm Gonna Stick Like Glue
Stick Because I'm...
Stuck On You
Hide In The Kitchen
Hide In The Hall
Ain't Gonna Do You No Good At All
'Cause Once I Catch Ya
And The Kissin' Starts
A Team O' Wild Horses
Couldn't Tear Us Apart
Try To Take A Tiger
From His Daddy's Side...
(LAUGHS)
When you're ready to give up
just let us know, heh?
Whee!
...Uh-uh-uh...
Yeah!
(FAST-TEMPO DRUMMING)
(DRUMMING CONTINUES)
(SLURPS)
(FLAMES ROAR, AUDIENCE GASPS)
(APPLAUSE AND CHEERING)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
(LAUGHING)
This is you.
This is your badness level.
It's unusually high for someone your size.
We have to fix that.
Ay-yi-yi, Lilo!
Your dog cannot sit at the table.
Stitch is troubled. He needs desserts.
Oh, you didn't even eat your sweet potato.
I thought you liked them.
Desserts!
(SIGHS)
(PEOPLE LAUGHING AND CHATTING)
LILO: David!
I got a new dog.
- Oh! You sure it's a dog?
- Uh-huh.
He used to be a collie
before he got ran over.
Yum!
(GOBBLING)
- Hey...
- Blah!
Eww!
Howzit, Nani?
Did you catch fire again?
Nah, just the stage.
Listen, I was wondering
if you're not doing anything this...
David, I told you, I can't. I...
I got a lot to deal with right now.
I know. I just figured
you might need some time...
You smell like a lawn mower.
(EXHALES AND SNIFFS)
Look, I got to go.
The kid at Table 3's throwing poiagain.
Maybe some other time, okay?
LILO: Don't worry.
She likes your butt and fancy hair.
I know. I read her diary.
She thinks it's fancy?
(GRUMBLING)
Blech!
(SNIFFING)
(EXCITED GRUNT)
Oh! Mmm!
Aha! Look what I find! Get restraints!
- Right.
- Ow! Take that! Hurry!
Uh, hold still just a...
(PLEAKLEY SCREAMING)
(GASPING) Aah!
(GROWLING)
(NANl GRUNTING WITH EFFORT)
(SHOUTS)
- (GROWLS)
- (PLEAKLEY SCREAMS)
(SNARLING)
(COUGHING)
MAN: Hey, Nani!
- Is that your dog?
- Uh...
(PLEAKLEY WITH WOMAN'S VOICE)
All is well.
Please, go about your business. I'm okay.
Oh, your head looks swollen.
Actually, she's just ugly.
(NERVOUS LAUGHTER)
Darling... He's joking.
Ugly, look at me...
Uh, this is not working out.
- Uh, b-but...
- Mm-mm.
Yeah?
Well, who wants to work at this stupid...
Fakey luau anyway.
Come on, Lilo.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(OWL HOOTING)
Did you lose your job
because of Stitch and me?
Nah. The manager's a vampire
and he wanted me to join
his legion of the undead.
I knew it.
This is a great home.
You'll like it a lot.
(HISSES)
See?
Uh, Lilo...
Comfy.
(GROWLS)
- (GRUNTS) Hey!
- Hey!
What is the matter with you?
Be careful of the little angel!
It's not an angel, Lilo.
I don't even think it's a dog.
We just have to take him back.
He's just cranky because it's his bedtime.
NANl: He's creepy, Lilo.
I won't sleep
while he's loose in the house.
LILO: You're loose in the house
all the time and I sleep just fine!
Hey, what are you doing?
Stop that, Stitch!
(GROWLS)
Hey!
(GROWLING AND GRUNTING)
Look at him, Lilo.
He's obviously mutated
from something else.
We have to take him back.
He was an orphan and we adopted him!
What about "'ohana"?
He hasn't been here that long.
Neither have I.
Dad said 'ohana means family.
- Huh?
- 'Ohana means family.
Family means...
BOTH:... Nobody gets left behind.
Or?
Or forgotten.
I know. I know. I hate it
when you use 'ohana against me.
Mmm.
(GRUNTS)
(GIGGLES) Don't worry,
you can sleep right next to me.
(GROANS)
(EXHAUSTED SIGH)
(GROWLS)
(SNIFFING)
Look how curious the puppy is.
This is my room, and this is your bed.
(GRUNTS)
This is your dolly and bottle.
See? Doesn't spill.
I filled it with coffee.
Good puppy. Now get into bed.
(GROWLS)
Hey! That's mine!
Down!
(GRUNTS)
Mmm!
Be careful of that! You don't touch this!
Don't ever touch it!
(GROWLS)
(STITCH MUTTERING
IN ALIEN LANGUAGE)
(CLOTH TEARING)
No! Don't pull on her head!
She's recovering from surgery.
(GROWLS)
No! That's from my blue period.
(GROWLING)
(GULPS)
Mmm...
There.
(PURRING)
You know, you wreck everything you touch.
Why not try and make something
for a change?
(PURRS AND GRUNTS)
(STITCH HUMMING)
(MUTTERING)
- Ah!
- Wow. San Francisco.
(HUMMING)
(ROARING)
(GROWLING)
(IN HIGH VOICE) Save me!
Eek!
(CHOMPING)
No more caffeine for you.
(LAUGHING)
This little girl is wasting her time.
6-2-6 cannot be taught to ignore
its destructive programming.
(LAUGHING)
Ooh!
(LAUGHING) Push that over.
(LAUGHING)
- What are you doing?
- Nothing!
- Uh, say, I want to try it on.
- No!
Share! Let me try it!
Hey! Ow! You're just jealous
'cause I'm pretty!
(GASPS)
Don't move. A mosquito has
chosen me as her perch.
She's so beautiful.
(BUZZING)
Look, another one.
And another one! Why, it's a whole flock.
And they like me!
They're nuzzling my flesh
with their noses.
Now, they're, um, they're...
(PLEAKLEY SCREAMING PAINFULLY)
NANl: I think it might be a koala.
An evil koala.
I can't even pet it.
It keeps staring at me,
like it's going to eat me.
(GASPS)
DAVID OVER PHONE: Hello?
Nani?
Hello?
Are you there?
(GULPING)
(BURPS)
JUMBA: Now, this is interesting.
PLEAKLEY: What?
6-2-6 was designed to be a monster
but now he has nothing to destroy.
You see, I never gave him
a greater purpose.
What must it be like to have nothing...
Not even memories to visit
in the middle of the night?
Nah!
(SPUTTERS)
Hmm.
Hmm...
(GROWLS AND GRUNTS)
- (GROANING)
- (GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING CONTINUES)
(YAWNS)
That's the Ugly Duckling.
See? He's sad because he's all alone
and nobody wants him
but on this page,
his family hears him crying
and they find him.
Then the Ugly Duckling is happy
because he knows where he belongs.
Hmm...
(GROWLS AND GRUNTS)
LILO: Want to listen to the King?
You look like an Elvis fan.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
LILO: Nani.
Nani!
Uh... Yeah?
Look.
(RECORD SCRATCHES AND POPS)
(ELVIS PRESLEY'S VOICE)
We Can't Go On Together
With Suspicious Minds...
(JAWS CREAKING)
...Cious Minds...
(CREAKING)
...Can Build Our Dreams...
...On Suspicious Minds...
- (POUNDING ON DOOR)
- (GASPS)
(CREAKS, MUSIC STOPS)
(FRIGHTENED GASP)
Heard you lost your job.
Well, uh, actually, I just quit that job
because, you know,
the hours are just not conducive
to the challenges of raising a child...
- (SNARLING)
- (GRUNTS) Hey!
(GASPS) I am so sorry about that.
What is that thing?
That's my puppy.
Really?
(CRACKING NECK)
Thus far, you have been adrift
in the sheltered harbor of my patience,
but I cannot ignore you being jobless.
Do I make myself clear?
Perfectly.
And next time I see this dog, I expect it
to be a model citizen... Capiace?
Uh... Yes?
New job.
Model citizen.
- (PLINKS AND CLATTERS)
- Good day.
(ELVIS PRESLEY'S
"DEVIL IN DISGUISE" INTRO PLAYS)
You Look Like An Angel...
Mrs. Hasagawa?
I'm here to answer your newspaper ad.
- Elvis Presley was a model citizen.
- ...Walk Like An Angel...
I've compiled a list of his traits
for you to practice.
Number one is dancing.
I can't talk now, dear.
I'm waiting for someone to answer my ad.
That's why I'm here.
Hands on your hips.
Now follow my lead.
(DRUMBEAT)
Ooh-hoo.
...You Fooled Me
With Your Kisses...
Ah! That's my want ad.
I know!
...Heaven Knows
How You Lied To Me
You're Not The Way...
HASAGAWA: Whoa, whoa!
(THUD)
Why is everything so dark?
I am all about coffee.
- Let's move on to step two.
- ...Walk Like An Angel...
- Elvis played guitar. Here.
- ...Talk Like An Angel...
Hold it like this,
and put your fingers here.
(STRUMMING SOFTLY)
See? Now you try.
(PLAYING BLUES RIFF)
...And I make great cappuccinos
and lattes with...
I wish I could, Nani,
but I just hired Teddy
and with tourist season ending...
(PLAYING ALONG WITH ELVIS' SOLO
AIN "DEVIL IN DISGUISE")
(PLAYING LOUDLY)
(ALL GASPING)
(UKULELE PLAYING CONTINUES)
(PLAYING EXPERTLY)
(SONG ENDS)
- Concierge-er-ing is my life.
- ...You Look Like An Angel...
I just love to answer phones...
- This is the face of romance.
- ...Walk Like An Angel...
She looks like she could use some lovin'.
...Talk Like An Angel,
But I Got Wise...
Oh, we might have something.
Good. Now kiss her.
(STITCH KISSES/WOMAN SCREAMS)
...The Devil In Disguise...
I'm sure Elvis had his bad days, too.
- I'm all about saving people?
- ...I Thought That I Was In Heaven...
Actually, I do think we have an opening.
- Really?
- Okay, this is it.
- ... But I Was Sure Surprised...
- Time to bring it all together.
Oh, that'd be so great!
You have no idea
how badly I need this job.
...The Devil In Your Eyes
- You're The Devil In Disguise...
- It's all you! Knock 'em dead!
(ELECTRICITY HUMMING)
...The Devil In Disguise
(PLAYING UKULELE SOLO
TO "DEVIL IN DISGUISE")
(PEOPLE CLAPPING IN RHYTHM)
(SCREAMS)
(STRUMS FINAL CHORD)
You're The Devil In Disguise...
(WHIMPERING)
- Don't crowd him!
- ...Oh, Yes, You Are
The Devil In Disguise...
(SNARLING)
(GASPS AND SCREAMS)
- The Devil In Disguise, Oh, Yes...
- Hey, knock it off!
- (SNARLS)
- (MAN YELLS)
(PANICKED SCREAMING)
(SNARLING HISS)
(SCREAMING FADES)
(MELANCHOLY MELODY PLAYS)
(SIGHING)
Hey, Lilo!
Howzit... Nani?
We've been having a bad day.
Hmm...
Hey, I might not be a doctor
but I know that there's no better cure
for a sour face
than a couple of boards
and some choice waves.
What you think?
I think that's a great idea.
MAN: Aloha E, Aloha E
CHORUS: Aloha E, Aloha E
'Ano'ai Ke Aloha E
Aloha E, Aloha E
'Ano'ai Ke Aloha E...
(DRUM BEATS
MEDIUM TEMPO RHYTHM)
(STRINGED INSTRUMENT
PLAYING UPBEAT MELODY)
(LILO GIGGLING)
There's No Place I'd Rather Be
CHORUS: Than On My Surfboard
Out At Sea
Lingering In The Ocean Blue
And If I Had One Wish Come True
I'd Surf Till The Sun Sets
Beyond The Horizon
Awikiwiki, Mai Lohilohi
Lawe Mai I Ko
(GASPING/CHATTERING)
MAN AND CHORUS: Flying By
On A Hawallan Roller Coaster Ride
(INSTRUMENTAL RIFF PLAYS)
(YELPS)
Awikiwiki, Mai Lohilohi
Lawe Mai I Ko Papa He'e Nalu
Pi'i Na Nalu, La Lahalaha
O Ka Moana, Hanupanupa
- Whoo!
- Lalala I Ka La Hanahana
- Me Ke Kai Hoene
- Yeah!
- Helehele Mai Kakou E
Hawallan Roller Coaster Ride
There's No Place I'd Rather Be
Than On A Seashore Dry, Wet Free
On Golden Sand Is Where I'd Lay
And If I Only Had My Way
I'd Play Till The Sun Sets
Beyond The Horizon
Lalala I Ka La Hanahana
Me Ke Kai Hoene I Ka Pu'e One
It's Time To Try
The Hawallan Roller Coaster Ride
(LILO LAUGHING)
Hang Loose, Hang Ten,
Howzit, Shake A Shaka
No Worry, No Fear,
Ain't No Biggy, Brahda
Cuttin' In, Cuttin' Up,
Cuttin' Back, Cuttin' Out
Front Side, Back Side,
Goofy-footed, Wipe Out
Let's Get Jumpin',
Surf's Up And Pumpin'
Coastin' With
The Motion Of The Ocean
Whirlpools Swirling,
Cascading, Twirling
Hawallan roller Coaster Ride...
(MELODY CONTINUES)
Oh, can't complain, Mom.
I'm camping out with a convicted criminal
and, uh... Oh, I had my head
chewed on by a monster!
Wait... Something is not right.
6-2-6 is returning willingly to water.
- (COMMUNICATOR BEEPING)
- Oh, hold on, Mom, another call.
(BEEPS, PLEAKLEY YELPS)
Mr. Pleakley, you are overdue.
I want a status report.
Oh, uh, things are going well.
He cannot swim!
Things are going well.
Jumba, aren't they going well?
Why will he risk drowning?
Jumba? Jumba, help me out here.
I would have expected you back
by now, with 6-2-6 in hand.
Just a few things left to pack
and, uh, we'll be...
Hang up.
(BEEPS)
- We are going swimming.
- Huh?
(PLEAKLEY YELLING)
MAN: There's No Place
I'd Rather Be
CHORUS: Than On My Surfboard
Out At Sea
Lingering In The Ocean Blue
And If I Had One Wish Come True
MAN AND CHORUS: I'd Surf Till
The Sun Sets Beyond The Horizon
Awikiwiki...
(GASPING)
Lawe Mai I Ko Papa He'e Nalu
(SCREAMING)
Flying By On
A Hawallan Roller Coaster Ride
Awikiwiki, Mai Lohilohi
Lawe Mai I Ko Papa He'e Nalu
Pi'i Na Nalu, La Lahalaha
O Ka Moana, Hanupanupa
Lalala I Ka La Hanahana
- Yeah!
- Me Ke Kai Hoene
Helehele Mai Kakou E
(YELLING)
Hawallan Roller Coaster Ride
(GASPS)
Lilo!
What happened?
Oh... Some lolo must have
stuffed us in the barrel.
Where's Stitch?
(GASPING)
- (YELLING)
- Get off of her!
What happened?
Stitch dragged her down.
(GURGLING)
(ALL GASPING)
We lost Stitch!
(INHALING DEEPLY)
(MUFFLED GRUNTING)
(BOTH YELLING)
(CRASHING)
(PANTING)
(GURGLING)
Lilo? Lilo, look at me.
Look at me, baby. Are you hurt?
No.
(GASPS AND GRUNTS)
(DAVID PANTING)
He's unconscious, but I think he's alive.
(CHOKING AND COUGHING)
(GROWLING)
(SNARLING)
David, take Lilo.
This isn't what it looks like.
We were... It-it's just that...
I know you're trying, Nani,
but you need to think about
what's best for Lilo...
Even if it removes you from the picture.
I'll be back tomorrow morning for Lilo.
I'm sorry.
(MELANCHOLY MELODY PLAYS)
Nani? Is there something I can do?
No, David.
Uh, I need to take Lilo home now.
We have a lot to talk about, you know.
Thanks.
You know, I really believed
they had a chance.
Then you came along.
(GENTLE THEME PLAYS)
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(QUACKS)
(CHEEPING)
(QUACKING)
Lilo, honey...
We have to, uh...
Don't worry. You're nice,
and someone will give you a job.
I would.
(SIGHS)
Come here.
(HAMMOCK CREAKS)
Aloha Oe
E Ke Onaona Noho
I Ka Lipo
One Fond Embrace
A Ho'i A'e Au
Until We Meet Again.
(WIND BLOWING)
(DREAMY TUNE PLAYING)
(WIND GUSTING)
LILO: That's us before...
It was rainy, and they went for a drive.
What happened to yours?
I hear you cry at night.
Do you dream about them?
I know that's why you wreck things
and push me.
Our family's little now
and we don't have many toys,
but if you want, you could be part of it.
You could be our baby
and we'd raise you to be good.
"'Ohana" means family.
"Family" means nobody gets left behind
but if you want to leave, you can.
I'll remember you, though.
I remember everyone that leaves.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING SOFTLY)
(SWEET, GENTLE MELODY PLAYING)
L... L...
Lost.
I'm lost.
(MELODY ENDS)
PLEAKLEY: Help!
I don't like the ocean!
(WHIMPERS)
(SCREAMS)
Oh, look, a friendly little dolphin.
(COUGHS) They helped sailors in the war...
It's a shark!
It's a shark, and it ain't friendly!
It looks like a dolphin.
Tricky fish! Tricky fish!
Oh, octopus, come and help me?
An octo... Octopus is worse than a shark!
I hate this planet!
(COUGHS)
(WAVES CRASHING)
(GASPING)
JUMBA: Oh...
Little monster!
(COMMUNICATOR RINGING)
(BEEPS)
Uh, Agent Pleakley here.
I have lost patience with you both.
Have you captured 6-2-6 or not?
Um...
Uh-uh...
Consider yourselves fired and prisonbound.
Your incompetence is
nothing short of unspeakable!
- (BEEPS OFF)
- But, uh... Mm...
(SOBBING)
We're fired!
Now we do it my way!
Your way? (SNIFFLES)
Oh... Uh, wait!
It seems I have overestimated
Jumber and Blinkley.
Uh, Jumba and Pleakley.
Whatever. The mission is in jeopardy.
This could be your chance
to redeem yourself, Captain Gantu.
How soon will you be prepared to leave?
Immediately.
(MOANING)
- (LEAVES RUSTLING)
- (GASPS)
(GASPS)
(CHUCKLING) Don't run.
Don't make me shoot you.
You were expensive.
Yes. Yes, that's it. Come quietly.
Mm... Waiting.
For what?
(CRUNCHES)
Family.
Ah!
You don't have one.
I made you.
Oh... Maybe I could...
You're built to destroy.
You can never belong.
Now come quietly
and we will take you apart.
No, no, no, no, don't, don't run!
Don't run!
(GROANS)
(SIGHS)
(GENTLE MELODY PLAYS)
Lilo.
(SNIFFLES)
I didn't hear you get up.
Baby, what's wrong?
Stitch left.
Really?
It's good he's gone.
He didn't want to be here, anyway.
We don't need him.
(SIGHS)
Lilo...
Sometimes you try your hardest
but things don't work out
the way you want them to.
Sometimes things have to change
and maybe sometimes
they're for the better...
Even if...
(KNOCKING)
DAVID: Nani!
(PANTING)
- David!
- I think I found you a job.
You what?
Old man Kukhkini's store,
but we got to hurry.
Oh, um, okay. Lilo?
Baby, this is really important.
I need you to stay here for a few minutes.
I'm going to be right back.
Lock the door
and don't answer it for anyone, okay?
Things are finally turning around.
Aw, David, I owe you one.
That's okay.
You can just date me,
and we'll call it even.
(WEAPON FIRING)
Come back here, you little...
(GRUNTING)
(FRANTIC PANTING)
Stitch?
What is it?
Shh!
(LOUD THUD, STITCH GASPS)
Oh, hiding behind your little friend
won't work anymore.
Didn't I tell you?
We got fired this morning.
(LAUGHING)
New rules.
(GRUNTING)
- Ha!
- Ooh.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, ooh! Ow! Ow! Ow!
(RICOCHETING)
ELVIS PRESLEY: You Ain't Nothin'
But A Hound Dog...
What are we going to do?
...Cryin' All The Time...
Ooh! I love this song!
- (ALIEN WORD)
- Pliers.
- Screwdriver.
Check.
Come out, my friend
from whomever you're hiding behind.
...Well, You Ain't Never
Caught A Rabbit
And You Ain't No Friend Of Mine...
What the...
- Ooh!
- (LAUGHING)
Come on! What's the big deal?
(SHOUTS IN ALIEN LANGUAGE)
I'll put you back together again.
I'll make you taller and not so fluffy!
I like fluffy!
No... No...
No!
(SPEAKS ALIEN LANGUAGE)
Oh, leave my mother out of this!
(GROANS)
You could do with a makeover.
I tried to give you my good looks,
but let's face it, something went wrong.
No!
(STITCH SNARLING)
(JUMBA GRUNTING)
Quick! Follow me! If we make it to...
- You're alive!
- They're all over the place!
(JUMBA LAUGHS)
Running away? Here... Let me stop you.
(YELLS, GULPS)
You always get in the way!
Where's the girl?
What have you done to the girl?
LILO: Hello? Cobra Bubbles?
Aliens are attacking my house.
No, no, no! No aliens!
Blue punch buggy!
- (SPUTTERING)
- No punch back.
(HORN BEEPS)
They want my dog!
There's no need to alert the authorities.
Everything's under control.
Lilo, who was that?
Oh, good, my dog found the chainsaw.
Lilo! Don't hang...
(LAUGHING)
(STITCH SCREECHING,
CHAINSAW BUZZING)
Ha!
You shouldn't play with guns.
- Oh, okay.
- Thank you.
(GUN WHINING IN OVERLOAD)
Oh, I just remembered. It's your birthday!
Happy birthday!
- Merry Christmas!
- It's not Christmas.
Happy Hanukkah!
We're leaving Stitch?
Trust me. This is not going to end well.
- One potato.
- Two potato.
- Three potato.
- Four.
- Five potato.
- Six potato.
Seven potato, more.
(ALTERNATING) My... Mother...
Told... Me... You... Are... It.
Oh, I win!
(EXPLOSION THUNDERS)
(THUD)
(PLEAKLEY YELLING)
Thanks. Mahalo plenty.
You won't be disappointed.
I'll show up early to help
with the morning deliver...
(SIREN WAILING, HORN BLARING)
Oh, don't turn left.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
No.
(GROANING)
(GASPS)
One of them had a giant eye
in the middle of his face.
Oh, Lilo!
Please don't do this.
BUBBLES: You know I have no choice.
No! You're not taking her!
I'm the only one who understands her!
You take that away,
she won't stand a chance!
You're making this harder
than it needs to be.
You don't know what you're doing!
She needs me!
Is this what she needs?
It seems clear to me that you need her
a lot more than she needs you.
Lilo! Lilo!
(NANl IN DISTANCE) Lilo!
(BUBBLES IN DISTANCE) Lilo!
NANI: Lilo!
BUBBLES: Lilo!
(GASPS)
You ruined everything.
You're one of them?
- (GRUNTS)
- Ooh!
Get out of here, Stitch.
- (TWIG SNAPS)
- (GASPS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Surprise!
(LAUGHING)
And here I thought
you'd be difficult to catch.
Ho-ho-ho. Silly me.
Lilo?
- (FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
- Lilo!
(SCREAMS)
(STITCH GROWLING)
(GASPS)
(CONTAINER BEEPS)
There you go, all buckled up for the trip.
And, look, I even caught you
a little snack.
(GASPS)
(GANTU CHUCKLING)
No! Stop!
(ENGINES REVVING)
(GRUNTING AND GROWLING)
(ENGINES WHIRRING)
(STITCH YELLING)
Lilo.
(GROANING)
Aah!
Okay, talk.
I know you had something to do with this.
Now where is Lilo?
Talk! I know you can.
(GROANS)
Okay, okay.
(SHRIEKS)
- (GROANS)
- Where's Lilo?
(SIGHS) Lilo...
(STITCH YELLS)
(LAUGHING)
Now all your washing is up!
You're under arrest! Read him his rights.
Listen carefully.
(STITCH GRUNTING)
(JUMBA LAUGHING)
PLEAKLEY: Hello? Galactic command?
Experiment 6-2-6 is in custody.
We'll wait right here.
(BEEPS OFF)
(JUMBA LAUGHING)
(RAGGED GASP)
(GROANS)
(LAUGHS)
Huh?
(WHISPERING) Don't interact with her.
Where's Lilo?
Who? What?
Lilo... My sister.
Uh, sorry, we do not know anyone
by this, uh...
Lilo! She's a little girl, this big!
She has black hair and brown eyes
and she hangs around with that thing!
Uh...
(SIGHS)
We know her.
Bring her back.
Oh, we can't do that. Uh-uh.
That would be a misuse
of Galactic resources.
See, problem is...
We're just here for him.
So she's gone?
Look at the bright side.
You won't have to yell at anyone anymore.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
(SIGHS)
(SOBBING)
Come.
(SOBBING CONTINUES)
'Ohana.
- Huh?
- Hey! Get away from her.
No! What did you say?
'Ohana means family.
Family means...
BOTH: Nobody gets left behind.
Or forgotten.
Yeah.
Hey... (SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE)
What?
After all you put me through
you expect me to help you just like that?
Just like that?
Ih.
Fine.
Fine? You're doing what he says?
Uh, he's very persuasive.
Persuasive? What exactly are we doing?
- Rescue.
- We're going to get Lilo?
Ih.
(ENGINE RUMBLING)
Oh, good! I was hoping to add theft,
endangerment
and insanity to my list of things
I did today.
(LAUGHS) You, too?
(LAUGHING)
(GASPS) Oh! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
What? Did you think we walked here?
(ALARM CHIRPS)
This is Gantu,
requesting hyperspace clearance.
COMPUTER VOICE:
Stand by for clearance.
(ENGINES RUMBLING)
(SNIFFLES)
(ENGINES ROARING)
(ENGINES WHINING)
(BRASS FANFARE PLAYS)
COMPUTER VOICE:
Clearance is granted on vector C-12.
Connect me to the Grand Councilwoman.
GRAND COUNCILWOMAN:
Gantu, what's going on?
I thought you'd like to know
that the little abomination is... Is...
(SPACESHIP HORN PLAYS
"LA CUCARACHA")
(SQUEAKING ON GLASS)
(SCREAMS)
GRAND COUNCILWOMAN:
Yes, Captain?
(GRUNTING)
I'll call you back.
(ENGINES WHOOSHING)
How did you get out of there?
So what exactly are we doing?
Don't worry, is all part of plan.
We are professionals.
Hey! Get that out of your mouth!
(SHRIEKS)
Hold on!
(GRUNTS)
Okay, is show time!
(LAUGHING)
(WHOOSHING)
This is it!
(YELLING)
Go! Go! Go!
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
(GROWLING)
Little savage! Get off my ship!
(STITCH YELLING)
Stitch!
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(CROAKS)
Computer, locate experiment 6-2-6.
COMPUTER: 6-2-6 located.
We finish this now.
Stitch is unconscious.
- What do we do now?
- We stay close. Hope for a miracle.
That's all we can do.
(ENGINE WHOOSHING)
(CROAKS)
No!
Don't leave me, okay?
Okay.
(HORN HONKING)
(RUMBLING)
Okay.
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
COMPUTER: Target 6-2-6 is in motion.
Speed is 84.
Impossible!
(HORN BLARING)
- Stitch!
- Hmm?
(ENGINES ROARING)
Abomination.
Stupidhead.
Yee-haw!
- (LAUGHING) Aloha!
- (GRUNTS)
You're vile! You're foul! You're flawed!
Also cute and fluffy!
(GANTU YELLING)
You came back.
Nobody gets left behind.
(KISSES)
(SCREAMS) Lilo!
Good dog.
(WHOOPING)
(GASPING)
Auwe!
LILO: David!
Hey, Lilo.
Can you give us a ride to shore?
Uh...
Sure! But I have to make two trips.
So you're from outer space, huh?
I heard the surfing's choice.
We have 6-2-6.
Take him to my ship.
- Leave him alone.
- Hold on.
- Grand Councilwoman, let me explain.
- Silence!
I am retiring you, Captain Gantu.
Actually, credit for the capture
goes to...
Goes to me.
You'll be lucky if you end up
on a Fluff Trog farm
after we sort this thing out.
Uh...
I think I should...
You! You're the cause of all this!
If it wasn't for your Experiment 6-2-6,
none of this...
- STITCH: Stitch.
- What?
My name Stitch.
Stitch, then.
If it wasn't for Stitch...
Does Stitch have to go in the ship?
Yes.
Can Stitch say good-bye?
Thank you.
Who are you?
This is my family.
I found it all on my own.
It's little and broken... But still good.
Yeah. Still good.
Does he really have to go?
(SIGHS)
You know as well as I
that our laws are absolute.
I cannot change
what the council has decided.
Lilo, didn't you buy that thing
at the shelter?
Hey!
Three days ago,
I bought Stitch at the shelter.
I paid two dollars for him.
See this stamp? I own him.
If you take him, you're stealing.
Aliens are all about rules.
You look familiar.
CIA. Roswell. 1973.
Ah, yes. You had hair then.
Take note of this.
This creature has been sentenced
to life in exile,
a sentence that shall be
henceforth served out here...
On Earth...
And as caretaker
of the alien life-form, Stitch,
this family is now
under the official protection
of the United Galactic Federation.
We'll be checking in now and then.
I was afraid you were going to say that.
This won't be easy to explain
back at headquarters.
I know what you mean.
(QUIETLY) Don't let those two
get on my ship.
(ENGINES ROARING)
CIA?
Former.
Saved the planet once.
Convinced an alien race
that mosquitoes were
an endangered species.
Now, about your house...
(PLAYING ACOUSTIC UKULELE)
Wait.
(PLAYING AMPLIFIED UKULELE)
(UP-TEMPO ROCK BEAT PLAYS)
Lord Almighty,
I Feel My Temperature Rising
Ooh
Higher And Higher
It's Burning Through To My Soul
Baby, Baby, Baby
You're Gonna Set Me On Fire
Yeah
My Brain Is Flaming
I Don't Know Which Way To Go
- (TIMER DINGS)
- Yeah
'Cause Your Kisses Lift Me Higher
Like The Sweet Song Of A Choir
You Light My Morning Sky
With Burning Love
Mmm... Ooh, Ooh, Ooh
I Feel My Temperature Rising
Mmm
Help Me, I'm Flaming
I Must Be A Hundred And Nine
Burning, Burning, Burning
And Nothing Can Cool Me
(ENGINE WHIRRING)
Mmm
I Just Might Turn Into Smoke
But I Feel Fine, Yeah
'Cause Your Kisses Lift Me Higher
Like A Sweet Song Of A Choir
And You Light My Morning Sky
With Burning Love
Burning Love
Mmm
(INSTRUMENTAL BREAK)
Burning Love
It's Coming Closer
The Flames Are
Now Licking My Body
Won't You Help Me?
I Feel Like I'm Slipping Away
Oh, Yeah
It's Hard To Breathe
And My Chest Is Just A-Heaving
Mmm, Mmm
Lord Have Mercy,
It's Burning A Hole In Me
Yeah
'Cause Your Kisses Lift Me Higher
Like The Sweet Song Of A Choir
You Light My Morning Sky
With Burning Love
Burning Love
Burning Love!
I'm Just A Hunk,
A Hunk Of Burning Love
A Hunk Of Burning...
Love.
(POP BEAT PLAYS)
Do, Do, Do
I Just Can't Help
Falling In Love With You
Wise Men Say
Only Fools Rush In
But I Can't Help
Falling In Love With You
Shall I Stay?
Would It Be A Sin?
If I Can't Help
Falling In Love With You
Like A River Flows To The Sea
So It Goes,
Some Things Are Meant To Be
Take My Hand
Take My Whole Life Too
For I Can't Help
Falling In Love With You
Wise Men Say
Only Fools Rush In
But I Can't, I Can't Help
Falling In Love With You
Take My Hand
Take My Whole Life Too
But I Can't Help
Falling In Love With You
Oh, I Can't Help
Falling In Love
Falling In Love With You
That's The Way Love Goes
That's The Way It Goes
And My Whole Life, Too
I Just Can't Help
Fallin' In Love With You
That's The Way Love Goes
I Just Can't Help Myself
So Falling, Baby, For You
Falling In Love With You
That's The Way Love Goes
That's The Way It Goes
'Cause I Can't Help
Falling In Love With You
(ECHOING) With You...
(ROUSING ORCHESTRAL
ADVENTURE THEME PLAYS)
(ADVENTURE THEME ENDS)
(SLOW, GENTLE THEME PLAYING)